{
    "subject": "resource/Manhattan_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/director",
    "object": "resource/Woody_Allen",
    "human_readable": "The director of the Manhattan film is Woody Allen.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9530037641525269,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Woody Allen."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9176115989685059,
            "question": "Name a film that features Woody Allen as both director and actor."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9102801084518433,
            "question": "What is the title of a notable film directed by Woody Allen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8918415307998657,
            "question": "What is Woody Allen known for directing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8885771632194519,
            "question": "Is Woody Allen an actor or director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8390040397644043,
            "question": "Besides directing, what other roles has Woody Allen played in film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8138675689697266,
            "question": "Who directed the film Manhattan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.725527822971344,
            "question": "Which famous film is associated with Woody Allen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6261319518089294,
            "question": "What genre of films is Woody Allen known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5534391403198242,
            "question": "Has Woody Allen won any awards for his directing?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of the Manhattan film is Woody Allen.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8829_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of films is Woody Allen known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8829_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which famous film is associated with Woody Allen?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8829_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who directed the film Manhattan?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8829_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8829_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8829_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8829_142.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8829_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8829_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8829_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8829_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8829_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8829_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8829_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents confirm that Woody Allen directed the film \"Manhattan.\" Therefore, the statement \"The director of the Manhattan film is Woody Allen\" is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}